import 'question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. What is the traditional color associated with Christmas?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Green',
      'b) Red',
      'c) Blue',
      'd) Yellow',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. What is the name of the famous reindeer with a red nose?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Dasher',
      'b) Vixen',
      'c) Prancer',
      'd) Rudolph',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. Which country is credited with starting the tradition of putting up a Christmas tree?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) United States',
      'b) Germany',
      'c) England',
      'd) France',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. What is the traditional Christmas meal in the United States?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Turkey',
      'b) Ham',
      'c) Roast beef',
      'd) Chicken',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. What is the date of Christmas Day?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) December 24th',
      'b) December 26th',
      'c) December 25th',
      'd) December 31st',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. How many days are there in the Twelve Days of Christmas?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) 6',
      'b) 8',
      'c) 10',
      'd) 12',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. Which song is commonly sung at the end of a Christmas party or gathering?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) We Wish You a Merry Christmas',
      'b) Jingle Bells',
      'c) Silent Night',
      'd) Deck the Halls',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. What is the name of the character who tries to stop Christmas from coming in Dr. Seuss  book â€œHow the Grinch Stole Christmas?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Scrooge',
      'b) Grinch',
      'c) Santa Claus',
      'd) Frosty',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '9. What is the name of the famous painting by Leonardo da Vinci that depicts a woman?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Tulipt',
      'b) Orchid',
      'c) Rose',
      'd) Poinsettia',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '10. What is the name of the famous Christmas ballet featuring a young girl and her nutcracker prince?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Swan Lake',
      'b) Sleeping Beauty',
      'c) Giselle',
      'd) The Nutcracker',
    ],
  ),
];
